The Mortuary Assistant is a horror film directed by Jeremiah Kipp.
Rebecca Owens, a recent mortuary science graduate takes a
night shift job at River Fields Mortuary.
Initially, the job seems straightforward — embalming bodies,
completing paperwork, and keeping things tidy.
But once Rebecca starts working the night shift, things take a dark turn.
Rebecca Owens, played by Willa Holland.
Raymond Delver, played by Paul Sparks.
The Mimic, played by Mark Steger.
Grandma, played by Shelly Gibson.
Kelly, played by Keena Ferguson.
The Mortuary Assistant is an upcoming American supernatural horror film directed by
Jeremiah Kipp from a screenplay by Tracee Beebe and Brian Clarke.
Based on the 2022 video game by DreadXP, it stars Willa Holland and Paul Sparks.
The film is scheduled to be released on Shudder on February 13, 2026.
The film explores themes of night shift, based on video game, mortuary.
The tone is dark.